Tsuki here, the proportion genius of Workdol (The ultimate proportion genius is on standby) Today, I felt a bit insecure (For the views) I had no choice, it was for the views
(The saviors of views are here) Guys, come on out (Ahyeon & Asa / BABYMONSTER) Have you worked a part-time job before? I made udon like this at my mom's sister's shop (Udon) Oh really?
(Experienced hire) Welcome (No experience) She turned out to be experienced Why did you decide to appear on Workdol? Actually, I’ve been watching Workdol all the time, especially when I eat
(Production crew’s self-esteem boost) - I’ve said this was my pick to appear in - Really? They love it so much (So happy) Isn’t today’s shoot just awesome? You mean the vibe’s good? I’ll just move on
So, what’s today’s part-time job? What's today's part-time job? Spray Spray Spray It's at a perfume store - Wow - Yes (Don't spray the perfume!) (Perfume store part-timer)
(Heading to work fast) Let's go Hello Hello We don't have much time, (Lee Myung-geun (2nd year)) so change into our uniform and let's get straight to work
(Quick change because we're busy) What the heck? (Front row seat to the drama) What is this? But I don't even know what you guys are selling, or what kind of...
(Holibanum Jamsil perfume store) We're a domestic perfume brand (A niche fragrance brand born from the hands of a perfumer) If you try selling and get some training, you'll understand
all the charms of our products Since you're working at a perfume brand, do you have any special skills? I'm kind of (Famous nose) famous for my sense of smell Super nose So then Huu (Damn it...)
Guess what I ate? You didn't brush your teeth yesterday? (Super nose's sense of smell is legit) How did he know? (Moving inventory) - This way, please - Looks kinda heavy
(Starting to load and unload perfume) - Hello, Mr. driver - Hi there Just stack them up neatly Got it It's actually heavy Oh, the box angle's off (First cart done)
If I drop it, the perfume will break, right? Then I guess you won't get paid for today Oh my god (Drop it and bye-bye salary) How much is all this together? (Starting the second cart)
Nice, Ahyeon, you got this Whoa, let’s go! (Sliding sound) Oh no, it’s falling! No, no, no, no! This thing’s precious (Nervous) If even one breaks, there goes today’s pay Careful, careful
What if my arm snaps? - Ugh - I'm sweating (Totally worn out) That's it for today's strength training (Seriously... workout complete...)
(no exaggeration, suffering for real while moving) We're heading to our warehouse (Product inspection) One person will check, count the products, then record it Let's start Alright Got it
I seriously didn’t understand a thing (Workdol MC's level) - You didn’t get any of it? - Yes, I was listening, but... (Explanation again) Check if the anti-tamper sticker is attached properly
Put it back in neatly Count them and let me know (Old-school) Why aren’t you bringing them over faster? Oh, no (Inspecting) (Approved) Yes Good Check complete We’re running out of time
We really have to hold our breath right now Could you let us breathe a little, please? (Total boomer) It's getting harder to breathe No rest allowed We don't have time
(You should work too now) Tsuki, looks like you have to do it too (Everyone's hustling at work) 36 (36, all clear) - All done? - Yes That was fast Of course Of course Then,
(Haze) why don't you show us a trick? Show us (Doesn't back down) Please just once I want... (Outrageous trick) (Second round) Please don't kick me out (Break time) (After work, it's girls' tea time)
Honestly, to be real, your concerts are way bigger than ours Okay? (Oh... Ah...) But you know you can't ignore us at music shows, right? Still, seniority is seniority, you know? Yep
No, you got to greet us properly and when we run into each other at music shows, (Teaching BABYMONSTER discipline) I'll bow at a 90-degree angle But I heard there is some good news
(Homework time) But I heard there is some good news (Quick promo time) Let me just do a quick one Honestly, this is the main thing, right? No We're here just to do a part-time job today
(Then promo confiscated) Then maybe you don't need to do it We were building up to this, though? (BABYMONSTER - HOT SAUCE promo) It's got a bubbly 90s hip-hop vibe that's perfect for summer
(Interesting) (Self-promo) That's it for now (Whatever, tell us a fun story) Any fun stories? (Ahyeon's fun story) So I got caught eating ramen at work
They told me to write a reflection letter about how I ended up eating it So... (Already awkward) So I wanted some ramen so I went to the convenience store, but now I had to write about it in detail
(Ahyeon's reflection) I bought ramen I sprinkled in the powder I ate some ramen, and it was tasty. That's it, right? (Unexpected recipe drop) I wrote it like that and got scolded
(Remembering a funny convo) Same here, seriously (Uneasy) Yes Asa Yes Do you have two butts or one? Haha, that's so random (Butt victim) But seriously, Asa unnie thought it was really important,
so she went around asking every member about it for a while Oh really? - I think there are two - Why two? There's just one (There is one/ There are two) No, - you got to combine these - It's one
(There are two) But since there are two legs, there's kind of a split, you know? She says there's a split (Stop overthinking) But it could just be a wrinkle
(Store prep) Could you try doing a display? Please decorate it artistically (Starting to decorate the product) All right All right (Lime scent tester) Lime Here it is First, do this in a zigzag motion
(Unleashing artistic spirit) - In a zigzag motion - Nice (Store getting pretty crowded) - There are too many, way too many - We have a lot of scents There’s also a new scent launching soon
What’s the new one that’s coming out? The new one coming out is called Noir Banana (Noir Banana: Creamy vanilla-scented tobacco, dreamy smoky woody scent) Banana, banana-na ♫ (What the...?)
Banana banana-na ♫ Banana ♫ (Reality check) Potato (Workdol is tough) We got to start selling for real now (Perfume sales training) Usually, you look at the customer's vibe and recommend a scent
that you think would suit them So, I'll give it a try Okay This is a roleplay (Idol-looking customer enters) Hi, since it's summer, I'd love to smell something nice and fragrant instead of sweat
(Face-reading check) In that case, something that matches your image (Ginger Holiday: The fresh, subtle scent of lilac, clean soap fragrance) It's blended from 11 different scents
So if you try it, you'll notice ginger (Paradise) as the base but it's a really luxurious scent Wow, it's like deodorant How am I supposed to describe this scent? Just describe it however you feel
So, can I just say it's an expensive perfume? (Thinking) Smells like a fancy perfume Yes, that's right Do you want to seem fancy? (Recommendation) Since you look kinda cheap! That one’s a no-go
You just got to compliment no matter what (Next customer is a Japanese customer) Japanese customer What would be good? Can you speak Korean? (Can't understand) (Fancy +1) Gyaru (Cool +1) (Charisma +1)
(Kawaii +1) Sweet, maybe? (Escaping from training) I think that's enough for training When you sell after putting on the perfume,
(Strategy: seduce customers with fragrance) customers will get curious about our scent My top pick is the signature scent, Summer Break (Summer Break: A sweet and tangy half-cut peach scent)
It honestly just smells like you’re holding a real peach (Asa PICK Summer Break) So, we’re spraying this one, right? (Dousing themselves in perfume) It's too much That’s way too much
I want to go for a more luxurious vibe That's Ginger (Tsuki PICK Ginger Holiday) (Loaded with rich vibes) You know what I mean, right? Which one? Rose? Should we? Oh, Rose? Alright
(Ahyeon picks Rosy Blossom) Where should I spray this? Oh, seriously Geez Not on the face It's not a mist That scared me I thought it was a cosmetics commercial, for real
(Moisture fully recharged) - Did you see? - Yes, on your face (Welcoming guests) Welcome (Flustered) Hello Ta-da Welcome Welcome to Holibanum That was so touching You enjoyed it, right?
Okay, so now you just need to buy a perfume (Truly cold-hearted capitalism) I have to buy one? (Perfume newbie) But I don't really use perfume that much (Prefers mist) As someone
who doesn't use perfume often, I'd recommend Summer Break (Highly recommended) as the easiest one to start with What kind of scent is it? We got to spray it for her Tssk
(Ahyeon going all out with energy today) (Super satisfied) All done My hands feel so soft Ah Peach? Oh, yes, that's right Yes, that's true Do you have a boyfriend? No If you spray it, everyone will...
- What?! - Exactly (Turns around to check the scent) Who's that person? I could totally see the future (Congrats in advance) - Congrats - Does that mean I can get a boyfriend right away?
(Chance of getting back together) There’s even a perfume that can make your ex-boyfriend come back to you Was there an ex you wanted to get back together with? Huh? Guess there is!
(Video letter cliché) Send a message to him How are you doing? Oh my - Yes, I'm doing well - Oh my We were supposed to get a meal together Maybe later
(Looks like they still can't forget each other...) You haven't eaten yet? - They haven't eaten yet - They haven't eaten yet, really? What are you doing? Come get her right now
Then are you gonna buy it? (Capitalism) Then are you gonna buy it? Excuse me Are you gonna buy it? (Break-up line) Can I think about it a little more? Oh, of course, that’s totally fine
(Another goodbye...) We’ll be waiting No... - Don’t go - Don’t go You did so well Very well (Breakup prevention pro tip) Let me give you a tip At this store only, you get a 10% discount,
and if you buy a perfume, you get a free 9ml mini perfume Why didn’t you say that earlier? (Nervous) I was gonna mention it after seeing you sell something (Meanwhile, a customer walks in) Okay
1, 2, 3, 4 Welcome Welcome to Holibanum Do you have any recommendations? (Pink) It seems like you like pink stuff, so I'd like to recommend this perfume Rosy Blossom It's Brrrrlossom Blossom Blossom
(An introvert's survival story in a variety show) How is it? It's good - Something a bit lighter? - Something light Can I make a suggestion? (Excited) I nailed the point This bag Oh my
What comes to mind? Banana Banana Banana (Presenting Noir Banana) I thought of a banana. Here, take this Five Six Seven Eight (CM song playing) Banana, banana-na ♫ Banana, banana-na ♫
(Their performance reaching its peak) Potato Banana, banana-na ♫ How is it? Do you like the scent? Yes, it has a subtle banana fragrance (Total customer satisfaction) It's so natural
(Manager barges in) Please tell her about the benefits I already shared the secret move If you buy this, actually, the manager here will buy it for you He'll buy it for me?
(An insane 90% off) Just pay 10% (What a steal) thanks to a 90% discount If you want, you can get this manager (Manager included as a freebie) as a buy one, get one free deal I have a boyfriend
Oh really? Not even as a spare? (...You think?) That's tough So, will you make a purchase? Oh Yes (First successful sale) Thank you (Serving more customers) Do you have any sweet scents? Yes, we do
Yes, we do - It's no joke, seriously - Here, smell this (Sniffing) Whoa, flowers just bloomed behind you Roses (Quick purchase after the compliments)
(Next up is Office Girl) If you work at an office, there's a perfume that really suits you Ginger Holiday Wow, look at all that treasure in the back - Wow - What do you think? I love it
(Another quick purchase here) Thank you, have a great day We're actually high school students (Nice to meet you, friend) (Exam takers) Is there something that can clear your mind,
make you feel refreshed? (Noir Banana recommendation) This one Oh, awesome Seriously, I want to buy it It's 79,000 won Sorry (Quick release) Thank you Ahyeon is dead (Resurrected) Crazy energy Nope
No, I’m totally fine right now (Today’s last guest) Hello (Reading the room) Welcome - Hello - How do you two know each other? (Awkward pause) We’re a couple (Over-the-top reaction)
My heart just started pounding Ba-dum (Just using the reaction as an excuse to fool around) (Q. What kind of perfume do you want?) - What perfume? - Love?
Something that can make our love become a bit stronger? (We'll let you know!) - Just a moment to think - I’ll think about it Do you argue normally, occasionally? A little A little?
I think they need a sweet scent A touch of sweetness This one? This one? Summer Break (Adding some sweetness) (All done) Go ahead (Love is being restored) - Is it good? - Yes
I think this one’s the best Really? Would you consider buying it? Well, I wouldn’t just buy it, but Ahyeon, you sing so well (Extorting a song from Ahyeon) Ahyeon’s song?
Something that could make love grow even more (Glancing around) If it’s a dangerous love, you got to sing Dangerously (Charlie Puth - Dangerously No holding back) We hope you last long
(Stay tangled up, for real!) We hope your dangerous love lasts a long time (Off work) It's over (Time to go home) We're done Money, money Money, please (That thrill of getting paid) Thank you
Do whatever you want with this Ahyeon, anything you want (Opens envelope) Hourly wage is 12,000 won, you worked 6 hours, so that's 72,000 won, but they gave you a 10,000 won bonus
(Perfume store pay: 12,000 won hourly x 6 hours + 10,000 won bonus = 82,000 won total) So what are you gonna do with it? I'm going to put it into savings Every little bit adds up, you know
(Ambitious girl) I'm gonna buy something bigger later What about you, Ahyeon? Me? First, I’d save it up too (Saving up in my belly) and maybe use it for food or something
Part-time job recommendation score Should we talk it over together? I smelled so many scents - that I got a little dizzy - Dizziness But I also got to smell the scents that make people happy, right?
So I think it’s a job with a really high satisfaction level because of that Then (Perfume part-time job rating: 4.5/5 Smelling nice scents 5.0, smelling too much 3.5, getting happy with people 5.0)
For today’s ending pose, let’s play the Cleopatra game where you can go all in for first place (First!) Hi, Cleopatra The best potato chips in the world Hi, Cleopatra
The best potato chips in the world Hi, Cleopatra Oh no The best potato chips in the world Hi, Cleopatra The best potato chips in the world Patra the world's best... (Farewell this world...)
(Goodbye, Tsuki) (Why we live separately) Does everyone live separately? Or alone? Now we each have our own rooms, and the dorm is split into two places Have you ever fought with the members?
Back when we were trainees, when we were really young, You fought? we fought a lot Are you all living together in the dorm now? We all live alone This is veterans This is to keep the team together
(Billy’s dorm, full of energy) It was the company’s decision to keep the team together (T saves the world) Tsuki said that if a close friend committed a crime
while she was a cop, she wouldn’t arrest them (The police episode will be released next week) What if your girlfriend is on a date with you and secretly steals something right next to you?
I would probably just hit them with the taser instead of actually using it So Tsuki, you wouldn’t arrest them? (ENFP) How am I supposed to catch them? Say it's your boyfriend or girlfriend
Someone you love, like family or whatever (Sticky fingers ON) - Oh my - Ah, theft But you're a cop (ENTP) You're a cop, right? My boyfriend just stole something, and I think he should be arrested
(Strictly T) Really? I don't think I'd let it slide (ISTJ) If there's compensation money... (Bounty hunter)